wcities.com 2000-06-21

# wcities.com - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement for www.wcities.com

Wcities.com Ltd has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.wcities.com.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration, to bill the user for products and services, and for other purposes. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

This site contains links to other sites. **www.wcities.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

The company does not share individual identifying information with any partners. The sharing of information limited to only aggregate information.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected from our users is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected from our users is used to check the users' qualifications for registration and bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. Ads may contain cookies, and appear to be coming from our site, but in reality they are coming from our partners who are serving ads on our site. Our site does use cookies.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

##  Supplementation Information

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties.

##  Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

  1. You can send email to [members@wcities.com](mailto:members@wcities.com)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:
14-15 Grosvenor Crescent, Belgravia, London, SW1X 7EE, UK
  3. You can call the following telephone number: +44 (0) 207 594 4900

##  Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  1. email [members@wcities.com](mailto:members@wcities.com)
  2. send mail to the following postal address:
14-15 Grosvenor Crescent, Belgravia, London, SW1X 7EE, UK
  3. call the following telephone number: + 44 (0) 207 594 4900

##  Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact

Members Department Wcities.com Ltd 14-15 Grosvenor Crescent Belgravia London, SW1X 7EE, UK [members@wcities.com](mailto:members@wcities.com)
